n95users.com 2011-11-20

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for NokiaUsers.net**

The privacy of our visitors to NokiaUsers.net is important to us. At NokiaUsers.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit this domain, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practices, and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 

  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Site Goals  **  
NokiaUsers.net was designed to give all Nokia owners a chance to collaborate and share information regarding their mobile, while also offering numerous other services (software sales, tips and tricks, etc.) for your phone. If you have any questions regarding the site, feel free to contact us .
